<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>OSE3.2 on dwnwrd Universal</title><link>https://dwnwrd.github.io/tags/OSE3.2/</link><description>Recent content in OSE3.2 on dwnwrd Universal</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dwnwrd.github.io/tags/OSE3.2/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>How to List Tags On Redhat Registry Images</title><link>https://dwnwrd.github.io/blog/2016/07/11/List-Tags-On-Redhat-Registry-Images/</link><pubDate>Mon, 11 Jul 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dwnwrd.github.io/blog/2016/07/11/List-Tags-On-Redhat-Registry-Images/</guid><description>Ever gone to RedHat&amp;rsquo;s container registry to search for an image and been left wondering what versions exist? Ever been frustrated by the inconsistent tag format? Is there a v or is there not a v? Me too.
Docker Hub has progressed to v2, while the RedHat registry is still v1 at the moment. As long as you use the right syntax, you can use curl to query the registry API and list the tags like this:</description></item><item><title>Deploy Hawkular Metrics in CDK 2.1 OpenShift 3.2</title><link>https://dwnwrd.github.io/blog/2016/06/16/Deploy-Hawkular-Metrics-in-CDK-2.0-OpenShift-3.1/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dwnwrd.github.io/blog/2016/06/16/Deploy-Hawkular-Metrics-in-CDK-2.0-OpenShift-3.1/</guid><description>Update! I failed with CDK 2.0, but CDK 2.1 works with some fiddling.
In my last post I installed Red Hat Container Developer Kit to deploy OpenShift Enterprise using Vagrant. But now I want to add Hawkular Metrics to that deployment.
Deploy Metrics Refer to the docs for deploying metrics in OSE.
Login to the vagrant CDK VM before continuing
$ cd ~/cdk/components/rhel/rhel-ose/ $ vagrant ssh $ oc login Authentication required for https://127.</description></item><item><title>Getting Started With RedHat Container Development Kit</title><link>https://dwnwrd.github.io/blog/2016/06/16/Getting-Started-With-RedHat-Container-Development-Kit/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dwnwrd.github.io/blog/2016/06/16/Getting-Started-With-RedHat-Container-Development-Kit/</guid><description>The RedHat Container Developer Kit allows you to deploy OpenShift on your laptop for easier testing and development. Here is how to deploy it.
Register as a RedHat Developer Obtain a RH login
Place credentials in ~/.vagrant.d/Vagrantfile to enable updates for VMs by automatically registering with RedHat Subscription Manager
Vagrant.configure(&amp;#39;2&amp;#39;) do |config| config.registration.username = &amp;#39;&amp;lt;your Red Hat username&amp;gt;&amp;#39; config.registration.password = &amp;#39;&amp;lt;your Red Hat password&amp;gt;&amp;#39; end Mac OS X Prereqs Install pre-reqs:</description></item><item><title>Upgrading OpenShift Enterprise from 3.1 to 3.2</title><link>https://dwnwrd.github.io/blog/2016/05/17/OpenShift-Enterprise-Upgrade-3.1-to-3.2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 17 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://dwnwrd.github.io/blog/2016/05/17/OpenShift-Enterprise-Upgrade-3.1-to-3.2/</guid><description>Upgrading from OSE 3.1 to 3.2 using the playbook went quite well for me, but there were a few issues to sort out.
The issues were related to:
ip failover had to be updated manually there was about 5 minutes downtime during the upgrade updates to image streams docker error messages updated policy and role bindings build strategy Source is not allowed hawkular metrics Upgrade Process Following the directions is pretty straight forward.</description></item></channel></rss>